Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
This is Jacob Barnes reporting live for
AMT news from the St. Louis White House
where mourners
are being allowed in
to pay their respects
to the late President.
As we await further details
in the apparent suicide
of Jeffrey Michener.
AMT news has confirmed that
the American hostages in Asia
have been rescued.
It is unclear whether the President
was aware of this good news
at the time of his death.
In the absence of any
final note or message.
we can only speculate.
It seems that the pressures
of his embattled agenda.
coupled with this
network's revelations
of his culpability in the
Doak Stadium disaster.
may have proved too much
for the President to bear.
Vice President Oliver just
transferred to the C-130 in Panama.
He should be on the ground in
St. Louis in four and a half hours.
Is Judge Watkins on board?
She's administering the
oath of office as we speak.
Good. That's good.
Please gather all of
our background and intel
on Peng and our Asian players.
President Oliver's gonna
need to get up to speed
before he speaks to
the regional leaders.
Yes. ma'am.
I've served under
six presidents.
Jeffrey Michener is the only
one I ever shook hands with.
The people of new China send
our deepest respect and condolences
to our brothers and
sisters in America.
It is with great sadness
that we have learned of
the death of President
Jeffrey Michener.
President Michener
was an important ally.
He's still in the mansion.
There's no way we're
getting back in there.
if that's what you are thinking.
We're in Tomahawk range.
Tom. we don't even
know if he's actually there.
He might have released this
video to bait us into attacking him.
Happy to call that bluff.
Okay. you take Peng out.
his number two continues
with whatever their agenda is.
and we've just started a hot war
without knowing what their plans are.
why those boats are so important
to him. what he's smuggling.
She's right. Much as I'd like
to take Peng out right now.
we gotta find Wu Ming
first. get to the bottom of this.
That son of a bitch has been
pummeling us for 10 rounds.
And I'm not much in the mood
to wait for his knockout punch.
What about all the innocent
people in and around the mansion
when your Tomahawk hits.
We can't just assassinate
a foreign leader
without consulting with
the commander in chief.
Find me when you
get close to Shanzai.
He blames himself.
For what?
Pushing Michener too
hard. Before he was ready.
Did he?
Country needed a president.
Maybe we should find a
plane. Get Tom to St. Louis.
He could help Oliver get his
bearings. give him some credibility.
You saw him. He's
not going anywhere
until we finish this.
Obviously. Jeffrey
Michener's are big shoes to fill.
But Howard Oliver is
beloved here in St. Louis.
where. as mayor. he oversaw
the most effective
quarantine in the country.
saving over 100.000
people during the plague.
It wasn't the first time.
He tried to kill himself
on the Nathan James.
He slit his wrists.
When Captain Chandler found
him. he'd nearly bled to death.
I had no idea.
I was on the ship. I...
They kept it quiet.
Only the senior leadership knew.
Jeffrey told me when he felt
that he could finally trust me.
I'm telling you this because you
need to stop beating yourself up.
If anything. I'm the one.
I knew he was suffering.
I knew and I left him alone.
Were the two of you...
I'm so sorry. Allison.
This one's a bust. too.
Damn it.
Hey. Doc.
Is this something you need?
That's... That's. uh...
I don't even know what that is.
Dr. Scott never let me touch that machine.
But I'm getting warmer?
Yeah. sure.
Hello.
Hey. Doc. Looks like we
got a stowaway here. mate.
Okay.
This is very. very good.
This is a really good start.
Um.
could you guys start setting
this up over here for me?
- You got it.
- Thanks.
You wanted to see me?
Kyoko has something to say to
you. She asked me to translate.
She says that you saved her life. But
more importantly. you saved her son.
That was all Logan and
Rios. I didn't really do much.
She says she hasn't
prayed since she was a child.
But now she will every day.
for the doctors and for you.
No. please. You don't have to
get up. It's okay. Ma'am. it's...
She says you are a natural.
President...
Mr. President. please.
Seems like the weather
matches our mood.
- Welcome home. Mr. President.
- Thank you.
The world's lost a great leader.
But we. in this room. we've
lost a colleague and a friend.
You all served him well.
And I look forward to continuing
the work you began together
as we navigate our way
through this difficult time.
I'll need all of your
help getting up to speed.
But first. I'll need to
speak to Captain Chandler.
St. Louis connected. sir.
- This is Captain Chandler.
- Stand by for the President.
- Captain Chandler.
- Mr. President.
I am so very sorry. I know
how close you and Jeffrey were.
I hope that over time. I can
earn the trust and confidence
that you and he shared.
Yes. sir.
I have a lot to catch you up on.
We're currently approaching
the pirate haven of Shanzai
where we intend to find a smuggler
who goes by the name of Wu Ming.
We think he might
be able to help
fill in the blanks about
why our people were taken.
about ships painted
with black circles.
and what President
Peng is planning in Asia.
Sir. I intend to
complete the mission
that was given to me
by President Michener.
with your permission.
You have my permission
and my gratitude.
Thank you. Mr. President.
We're 27 nautical miles
southeast of Shanzai port. sir.
Vulture Team is standing by for
Captain Chandler and ready for infil
as soon as Nomad
has eyes on target.
All right. listen up. we got a
high-value target-capture mission.
After beach entry. we
silent-patrol to the target.
penetrate the perimeter defense.
and we capture that
son of a bitch Wu Ming.
We'll have an
immediate helo exfil.
Last time we were in
Shanzai. it got hot. fast.
So watch your six.
Nathan James. this is Nomad.
going feet dry. six
klicks from Shanzai.
- Sonar.
- Nothing on subsurface.
Radar tracking surface contact
bearing 2-5-8 heading 0-1-4 at 18 knots.
AIS classifies it as
a shrimp cutter. sir.
We are not taking any chances.
All stations continue to
track and monitor that vessel.
CNO on the bridge.
Did you get the go from POTUS?
He understands the importance
of what we're doing here.
but has requested
proof-of-life videos.
It's a morale boost
for back home.
Land team is waiting for you.
Nathan James. this is
Nomad. Flag on the play.
Shanzai is a bust.
The place is a fire pit.
The whole town?
Wiped out.
Nothing but ashes.
Nomad returning to ship.
He carpet-bombed
everybody to get one guy?
Peng levelled Shanzai.
Charred the place
to tie up loose ends.
We assume Wu Ming's dead.
But we still need to figure out
how he tracked all those ships.
Especially the ones he
wanted you to stay away from.
Any idea if he might have
had a backup outside Shanzai?
It's a Chinese proverb.
Wu Ming taught
me this when I asked
why he never pirated
the ships himself.
It means.
"When children travel far from
home mothers never stop worrying."
So he was a mama's boy?
He supported her.
his sister. the grandmother.
And you think he may
have stashed intel with them.
That way they could
carry on the business.
He could provide for
them. even in death.
It's the only good thing
I ever heard about him.
Took care of his family.
And where exactly might
we find Mama Ming?
Nathan James will
loiter over the horizon
while a VBSS team commandeers a
vehicle near the Beng Mu Chun inlet
and then heads inland to Chin
Ma to find Wu Ming's family.
Just awaiting
your approval. sir.
Yes.
Commander Green.
How are we doing on
those proof-of-life videos
from the rescued hostages?
The Nathan James crew
is working on them. sir.
But we are having some difficulty
with the visual signal on our end.
I can get the audio
recordings for you right away.
Audio isn't good enough.
We need to see faces.
The American people need
to see that we had a win.
Sort out that
technical glitch ASAP.
Yes. sir.
Okay. Miller. This is for
everybody back home
so they know you're
still taking up space.
All right. go
ahead. start talking.
Hey. Ma. Now. don't be scared. I
know my face is a little messed up.
but the doc promised
that I'll go back to being
just as pretty as I was before.
So. Freak from
Spider-Man. basically.
Okay. man. A little respect.
This is for my mother.
Hey. Ma. Now. don't be scared. I
know my face is a little messed up.
- but the doc promised...
- Can you see anything at all?
Just as pretty as I was before.
- Still nothing.
- So. Freak from Spider-Man. basically.
- Okay. man. A little respect.
- There it is again.
I miss you. Mom. I love you.
Isn't this the same problem
you were working on with Val?
Yes. But there's hundreds
of hours of data to analyze.
So we haven't been able to
figure out what's causing it.
With her gone...
Damn. System just crashed.
I need to run downstairs to
the communications room.
Hurry. Dennis. We
need to fix this. Please.
How are you holding
up over there?
Alisha.
I'm the one who found Michener.
Oh. my... Kara.
I'm sorry.
You are over there risking
your lives. I'm sitting at a desk.
- I shouldn't...
- No.
We need you there.
Now more than ever.
Vulture Team has
reached Chin Ma.
- ETA to target?
- Less than five minutes. sir.
Clear. Go.
That's MSS.
I guess Peng wants to
talk to Mama Ming. too.
Ah!
Well. he's still alive.
All teams. sitrep. over.
- Cooper. set.
- Green. set.
Taylor. go for entry.
Burk's got eyes on upper target.
I got the shot on
the lower. Burk. go.
Taylor. set.
Primary entry team. set.
All teams. on my count.
Three. two. one.
Execute.
How are you feeling. Wu Ming?
Grateful we saved your life?
He says you brought
them to his door.
It's you who got
everybody in Shanzai killed.
I didn't start this.
You and Peng did.
Why was Lau Hu torturing you?
Lottery tickets.
How the hell does lottery even work
now? There's barely any currency.
I've seen it in Hong Kong. mate.
People put in whatever they have.
A chicken. a bag of rice.
They get a ticket.
a number's drawn.
Whoever wins.
takes the entire pot.
After the proprietor skims
some off the top. of course.
Tell me about black
circles on ships.
He's hiding something.
What's so precious
about those marked ships?
Why would Peng
go to all this trouble?
Why are you still protecting Peng
after everything he's done to you?
I know nothing.
Nothing. Nothing!
That look like a
hull number to you?
Yes. it does.
These digits here.
these are coordinates
for the Strait of Malacca. the
biggest shipping lane in the region.
It's the intel Wu
Ming sells to pirates.
If each one of these lottery tickets
represents a ship and its location...
Jackpot.
Sir.
You all right?
I could have done
without Rivera's eulogy.
Seems like he's already
jockeying for favor.
I noticed that our lone senator was
conspicuously absent from the funeral.
I spoke to Beatty. There was an attack
on a ration card facility in Bellingham.
He's sitting on a powder keg
up there. He couldn't get away.
Maybe.
Or maybe he's sending a signal that
he's not in support of our administration.
Well. the Senator
wasn't particularly fond
of how the last president
used him as a rubber stamp.
- Meaning?
- Sir. you've been away.
I don't think you realize
what a mess this country is in.
Maybe they don't remember what
a mess we had five months ago
before Michener and the
James came home with the cure.
No. they remember. sir. And
they are grateful for the cure.
But that doesn't give the government
a free pass for everything else.
Especially since people think
that most of the decisions
that have come out of here
have been disastrous.
Hell. you can't even prove
you rescued your own people.
The pirates broadcast their faces
from a jungle across the globe
and you can't manage a Skype
call from a $3 billion warship?
We're working nonstop
on the issue. Mr. President.
I'm confident we'll
have it solved shortly.
Let's not lose the
forest for the trees.
We're all pleased that
the hostages are safe.
and we're sure
you'll sort that out.
The more pressing issue
is our domestic policy.
I think we can all agree
that Michener jumped too
quickly to federalize everything.
If you were to curb some of his
measures. I'm sure it will go a long way
to smoothing things
over with Senator Beatty
and the American people.
The ration card program has
been the chief cause of unrest.
And limits to bank withdrawals.
The people do not
want the government
interfering with how
they spend their money.
Come on. Alex. It's all of it.
The land claim issues
are just as contentious.
What do you all want?
To go back to dog-eat-dog?
That's appealing when
you're at the top of the heap.
But there are people
out there going hungry
while we are producing more
than enough food to feed everyone.
That's why President Michener
started those ration cards.
So that all of our citizens
can have their fair share
- of what they need to get...
- Commander Green.
If we need your advice as it
pertains to our military. we'll ask for it.
Sir. I know that
you were skittish
about instituting these
policies from the beginning.
It doesn't matter what I thought
then or if they're unpopular.
Are they working or not?
I think it's fair to say that
these policies are doing
more harm than good. sir.
What happened in there?
Everything we worked for. everything
President Michener stood for.
We're in a crisis. It's our job
to hold the country together.
You sat with the President
and wrote those policies.
You didn't fight for them.
If President Michener
couldn't make them work.
then Howard
Oliver certainly can't.
So you are going to let Oliver
capitulate to the regional leaders.
He just gave them
authority over local militias
without speaking
to Captain Chandler.
Chandler is the acting
head of our military.
and he never would
have allowed it.
Captain Chandler
is 12.000 miles away.
The regional leaders need to
be able to call their own shots.
If they can't control their
own regions. who will?
They are the ones stoking
the unrest. President Michener...
President Michener isn't here!
He took the easy way out.
So if they sit in that office
and they reverse every decision
that he made as president.
there's nobody to blame but him.
Sir.
Uh. thank you for coming down.
I've made some progress. sir.
but I still have more
questions than answers.
This is an image of our
cure from Dr. Scott's notes.
I've isolated the compound in
Takehaya and Kyoko's blood.
It's exactly the same as ours.
Structurally uncompromised.
as far as I can tell.
This is an image of the
red flu from Dr. Scott's files.
And this...
This is the virus
in Kyoko's blood.
It's different.
- Bulkier.
- Exactly.
That bulkiness is present
in Takehaya's virus as well.
The virus in their blood is
similar enough to the original
that my preliminary
tests identified it.
- But it is somewhat altered.
- A mutation.
I can't say for sure. But
whatever is causing the bulkiness
is preventing the
cure from working.
That means everyone on this ship
who has come in contact with Takehaya
- could be infected.
- That was my worry. too.
But none of us from the prison
camp have any symptoms.
I crossed the virus
in Takehaya's blood
with a sample of my own
and from several sailors
who had no contact with Takehaya.
Kyoko or any of us who were prisoners.
The bulkier virus
doesn't make us sick.
Somehow the cure in
us defends against it.
If Takehaya and Kyoko
both have the same cure.
why is the virus harming them?
I wish I knew. sir.
I'll keep digging.
We're at 19.83
North by 112.5 East.
Course 1-0-0.
speed 20 knots. sir.
There's a small landmass here.
which should provide cover
from hostile radar detection
while giving us a vantage point on
the shipping lane indicated on that card.
Helo is standing by
to execute flyovers.
We expect many vessels to have
AIS switched off on account of pirates.
She's Alpha-Charlie-Foxtrot
7-9-8-3-1-3-9-6.
Any other markings?
Uh. just a couple of dings
from a bad parking job.
No black dot.
No dice.
Is it possible the ship
already passed this location?
According to Wu Ming's
intel. it was last pinged
outside Hainan Harbor
yesterday at 2200 hours.
Even a wave-piercing catamaran
couldn't traverse this
shipping lane that quickly.
Captain.
Radar's tracking
small surface vessel
approaching our contact
point on the shipping lane.
Nomad. vessel
approaching south at 0-2-5.
Initiate flyover.
Roger that. Nathan
James. Making the turn.
I don't know about
this one. Captain.
What's wrong with it?
There's nothing wrong with it.
if you are on
spring break in Ibiza.
What the hell does that mean?
It's a 120-foot pleasure
cruiser. No cargo hold.
Wait a second.
Alpha-Zulu-Bravo-7-9-8-6-3-Lima-3-0-9.
That's it.
And we're staring at a big
old dark side of the moon.
Vessel Encore. 0-1-4. 22 knots.
This is US Navy warship 1-5-1
requesting to
board for inspection
in accordance with the
International Law of the Sea.
Vessel Encore. 0-1-4. 22 knots.
I say again.
This is US Navy warship 1-5-1
requesting to board for inspection
in accordance with the
International Law of the Sea.
TAO. surface tracks 7-2-8-7-1
increasing speed to 25 knots.
Captain. TAO.
Surface contact maybe
trying to make a run for it.
XO. let's stick our nose out.
let him know he has company.
OOD. increase speed to 25
knots. Come to 1.000 yards CPA.
TAO. surface tracks 7-2-8-7-1
coming to course 0-4-5.
increasing speed to 35 knots.
They're trying to evade.
Just turn starboard
and increase speed. sir.
Starboard ROC. fire MK-38. one
salvo warning shots across the bow.
Prepare countermeasures. But
do not. under any circumstances.
sink that ship. Not till
we know what's aboard.
Aye. Captain.
All stations. stand
by to re-engage.
Sir. he's changed course to 2-5-0.
He's headed for the Yanshi Atoll.
OOD. all ahead full.
Sir. we can't outrun him.
He's traveling at 36 knots.
And we can't go into the atoll.
the coral beds are too shallow.
XO. time to close the net.
Nomad. you are go for approach.
All right. boys and girls.
Let's drop in for a cocktail.
TAO. surface tracks
vessel. 1.000 yards.
Captain. TAO. Surface
contact 10 degrees relative.
Okay. don't do it.
buddy. Not a good move.
Don't do anything stupid.
- Cut your engine.
- Shit. man.
We are US Navy. Lay
down your weapon!
We don't want to hurt you. but
we will be boarding your vessel.
Nathan James.
vessel is surrendering.
Game over. asshole.
Is this even necessary. yo?
Tell us where Peng's cargo
is. and we'll stop right now.
Does this even look
like a cargo ship to you?
We tossed the whole vessel.
All we found were
a couple more M16s
and a case of Cristal.
See? What did I tell you?
If you got nothing to hide. then
why run from a US Navy ship?
It's the apocalypse. man.
All kinds of people get
into all kinds of boats
saying all kinds of shit.
You could have been
pirates. for all I know.
This is my boat. You
can't take it from me.
Oh. yeah? You got bills of
sales for those weapons?
Well. then you are in violation
of International Maritime Law.
The US Navy has the right
to place you under arrest
and commandeer this vessel.
Hell. no. This is my
baby. You can't do this. yo.
We sure can. yo.
You wanna keep your
precious ship. you start talking.
Americans.
So self-righteous.
Move.
Well. that's cocaine. heroin.
- How much more of this have you got?
- Five more crates.
Come on. yo. This can't
even be illegal anymore.
The people have suffered
enough. I'm just meeting needs.
Where'd you pick it up?
An island up at Hainan.
Chinese MSS dudes loaded me
up. I don't want to mess with them.
Peng doesn't bother with drugs.
Hey. what are you doing. yo?
You know what my suppliers will do
to me if even one of those is missing?
Shut up.
Holy shit!
The missile's clearly been
retrofitted since its manufacture.
Has to be a chemical
weapon of some kind.
He picked up those crates
100 miles southeast of Hainan.
Paraiso Island.
You sure that trafficker
didn't know what was in 'em?
He was perfectly happy being
a run-of-the-mill drug runner.
Nearly wet himself
when we reeled in this.
Those bomblets were designed
in the '60s to carry sarin.
What do you think the
range is on that missile?
Depending on the
weight of those bomblets.
I guess it could release high
enough to blanket a 20-mile radius.
You wanted to see me?
Back in Hong Kong. you
mentioned seeing some missiles.
Yellow with red tips.
These are the same ones
Peng was moving in Guangzhou.
The day my brother was killed.
Oh!
Green mist.
Kyoko in her fever. she was murmuring
about a green mist that came in the night.
The active ingredient in the green
powder is a specially designed lectin.
It's binding to the
glycoproteins of the red flu.
That's why the virus looks
bulkier. It hasn't mutated.
The lectin can create a
coating that shields the virus
from the effects of the
antibody that our cure produces.
I couldn't see it because I
didn't know what I was looking for.
- But if somebody already has the cure?
- Then they're safe.
You'd have to have the
lectin in your bloodstream first
to render the cure ineffective.
That's what Peng's hoarding.
He could fire those missiles
over uncured populations.
- So when the cure finally does arrive...
- It doesn't work.
That boat was headed
to Taiwan on a run.
Jesse saw the
missiles near Vietnam...
And my wife saw
the mist in Japan.
By the time we got to the
ports to receive the cure.
it was already too late.
That's right.
I would like to see my wife.
my son.
- Good evening. Mr. President.
- Commander Green.
That's correct.
The President would
like to keep these briefings
to senior advisors
for the time being.
We'll summon you if we need you.
We were welcomed
as heroes in Vietnam.
Everyone came out of
hiding to get the cure.
If they were exposed to this...
They'd spread out across the
country to pass on the contagious cure.
And if they were
exposed to the red flu.
spread that instead.
That was 10 days ago.
And we don't know how many
of these missiles there are.
So. now we know
what Peng's plan is.
It's genocide.
English -SDH
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today